[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Musician Huey Lewis appeared in the movie Back to the Future.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the villains henchwoman in A View to a Kill, who dies after switching sides?", "correct_answer": "May Day", "incorrect_answers": ["Waldina  Zell", "Persephone Brutus", "June Moon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the Pan Am Flight 759 disaster that happened on July 9, 1982?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["153 people were killed.", "There was only one survivor.", "It was flying from Miami to Las Vegas."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Finish this Irish saying: The far off hills are _______.", "correct_answer": "the greenest", "incorrect_answers": ["covered with clouds", "alive with the sound of music", "the farthest away"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This person, who became public announcer for the New York Yankees in 1951, appeared in the movies 61, It Could Happen to You,  The Scout and Anger Management.", "correct_answer": "Bob Sheppard", "incorrect_answers": ["Joe Buck", "Phil Rizzuto", "Michael Kay"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This character from the movie For Your Eyes Only, whose parents were killed by a pilot working for the villain, is James Bonds female ally.", "correct_answer": "Melina Havelock", "incorrect_answers": ["Christiane  Uhlenbeck", "Nora  Dobbs", "Aphrodite Themistoclou"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does King Julien the Lemur wish he could do in the 2008 animated movie Madagascar: Escape 2 Africa?", "correct_answer": "Whistle", "incorrect_answers": ["Dance", "Sing", "Fly"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Vegetarian diet is rich in these agents, found mostly in fruits and vegetables. They are known to fight free radicals,  thus slowing down the process of aging.", "correct_answer": "Antioxidants", "incorrect_answers": ["Essential oils", "Vitamins", "Cholesterol"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How much time did the astronauts from Apollo 11 spend on the lunar surface?", "correct_answer": "2\u00bd hours", "incorrect_answers": ["About 60 minutes", "5 hours", "35 minutes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are Chuck Nolands last words to his fiancee when he gets on the plain at the beginning of the movie Cast Away?", "correct_answer": "Ill be right back!", "incorrect_answers": ["I hope this plane doesnt go down.", "Marry me when I come back!", "Do not forget me!"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who usually is in charge of a US Army infantry company?", "correct_answer": "A captain", "incorrect_answers": ["A sargent", "A one-star general", "A colonel"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This scale was originally used to determine the level of consciousness after head trauma.", "correct_answer": "Glasgow Coma Scale", "incorrect_answers": ["Johnson Coma Scale", "Barnes Akathisia Coma  Scale", "Miller Coma Scale"]}]